# SAM KAUFFMAN

hello@samvk.com https://samvk.com

860-878-8669 West Hartford, CT 06107

#### SUMMARY

I'm a web developer who loves building apps and bringing designs to life. My go-to technologies right now include HTML5, CSS3, and JavaScript(ES8+) — amped with the help of React & Redux and **PostCSS** & Sass. Previously, I've also worked with jQuery, and some PHP and SQL.

Feel free to check me out on GitHub at https://github.com/samvk or take a look at my portfolio at https://samvk.com.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

# Software Engineer | Web Application Developer

Konica Minolta Business Solutions, Windsor, CT

2016 – Present

- Led a small team in the development and adoption of React & Redux and PostCSS for the new global app store
- Redesigned the app store for a modern look and better user-friendliness
- Worked closely with QA to improve the stability and user-interface of the store
- Technical Skills: HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript(ES8+), React, Redux, PostCSS, Sass

## Freelance Front-End Web Developer

Greater Hartford, CT

2015 - 2016

- Performing front-end maintenance and upgrades for existing websites
- Developing mobile-friendly responsive websites
- Basic back-end management

### **Technology Specialist**

March 2016 – November 2016

CREC Capitol Region Education Council, Greater Hartford, CT

- Troubleshooting and resolving issues related to computer software and hardware
- Performing desktop and laptop re-imaging tasks
- Installing software updates and hardware upgrades on end user machines

### **Mathematics Associate Instructor**

2015 - 2016

2011 - 2015

CREC MLC High School, Bloomfield, CT

- Supporting students in the strengthening of math skills and conceptual understandings
- Integrating technology into the classroom to help visualize, analyze, and interpret data
- Gathering school data to track long-term student growth

## **Easy Tech and Sales Associate**

February – September 2014

Staples Inc, Lancaster, PA

- Staying current on new technologies
- Resolving computer hardware, software, and operating system issues
- Determining and fulfilling client needs

# **Technical Assistant**

F&M Schnader Theatre, Lancaster, PA

- Operating sound board and A/V equipment
- Rigging audio systems and and troubleshooting lighting and rendering problems

#### **EDUCATION**

## Franklin and Marshall College

- May 2015 • B.A. in Technical Theatre and Design
- Graduated cum laude